americaint.com 2015-04-27

# Bulk Email Superstore's Client Services

PRIVACY POLICY:

eMarketing Solutions has always been committed to maintaining the accuracy, confidentiality, and security of your personal and corporate information. We have established Privacy Principles to govern our use of customer information. 

eMarketing Solutions does not sell, share or distribute Customer Information to any third party organization. 

Accountability   
eMarketing Solutions is responsible for maintaining and protecting customer information under its control. 

Identifying Purposes  
eMarketing Solutions does not collect personally identifiable information about visitors except when visitors specifically provide such information on a voluntary basis. For example, such personally identifiable information may be gathered from the registration process for subscription sites or services and in connection with content submissions, community postings (e.g., chat and bulletin boards), suggestions, and transactional areas. Such information may be used by eMarketing Solutions for the following purposes: contacting a subscriber regarding account status, changes to the subscriber agreement, special discounts, promotions, products offered and other matters relevant to the underlying service and/or the information collected. 

eMarketing Solutions values opinions and comments from visitors, so we occasionally conduct online surveys. These surveys are entirely optional for all visitors. Most frequently, the information is aggregated and used to make improvements to eMarketing Solutions web sites and to develop appealing content, features and promotions for visitors. Survey participants are anonymous unless otherwise stated in the survey. eMarketing Solutions reserves the right to perform statistical analyses of visitor's behavior and characteristics. In order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the site and to inform advertisers of such information as well as the number of visitors that have been exposed to or clicked on their advertising banners. eMarketing Solutions will provide only aggregated data from these analyses to third parties. Also, visitors should be aware that eMarketing Solutions may sometimes permit third parties to offer subscription and/or registration-based services through an eMarketing Solutions web site. 

eMarketing Solutions is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties and visitors should check the applicable privacy policy of such party when providing personally identifiable information. Visitors should be aware that when they voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information (e.g., user name, e-mail address) on the bulletin boards or in the chat areas of eMarketing Solutions sites, that information, along with any substantive information disclosed in the visitor's communication, can be collected, correlated and used by third parties. This information may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of eMarketing Solutions   

Consent  
The knowledge and consent of the customer are required for the collection, use or disclosure of customer information except where required or permitted by law. 

Limiting Collection   
The customer information collected must be limited to those details necessary for the purposes identified by eMarketing Solutions Information must be collected by fair and lawful means. 

Limiting Use, Disclosure and Retention  
Customer information may only be used or disclosed for the purpose for which it was collected unless the customer has otherwise consented, or when it is required or permitted by law. Customer information may only be retained for the period of time required to fulfill the purpose for which it was collected. 

Accuracy  
Customer information must be maintained in as accurate, complete and up-to-date form as is necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it is to be used. 

Safeguarding Customer Information   
Customer information must be protected by security safeguards that are appropriate to the sensitivity level of the information. 

Openness  
eMarketing Solutions is required to make information available to customers concerning the policies and practices that apply to the management of their information. 

Customer Access   
Upon request, a customer shall be informed of the existence, use and disclosure of their information, and shall be given access to it. Customers may verify the accuracy and completeness of their information, and may request that it be amended, if appropriate. 

Handling Customer Complaints and Suggestions   
Customers may direct any questions or inquiries with respect to the privacy principles outlined above or about our practices by contacting the designated person(s) accountable for privacy at eMarketing Solutions. 

If you would like to unsubscribe, please contact us through the contact us link on our website or call us at 954-975-2575.

©2000-2014 [Bulk Email Software](http://www.americaint.com/default.html) Superstore, All rights reserved.
